Finding Aid for Hunein F. Maassab papers, 1951-2002
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Research, 1951-1999
  - Laboratory Notebooks and Data
    - Genotyping and Sequencing
      - Genotype Films
        - CR 149 Aberrant NS Sequencing, undated (Box 27)
        - 32p -- Labeling Test, undated (Box 27)
        - Aviron Viruses, undated (Box 27)
        - B -- Striker, undated (Box 27)
        - Baylor Bivalent Study, undated (Box 27)
        - Bivalent Vaccine in Mice, undated (Box 27)
        - [Blank], undated (Box 27)
        - Blot Hybrid, undated (Box 27)
        - Class Gels --, 1990 (Box 27)
        - Collaboration with Mark Snyder, undated (Box 27)
        - Cox, Nancy, undated (Box 27)
        - D of IV R(-) Hypsin, undated (Box 27)
        - Dominance -- Youngner and Dowling, undated (Box 27)
        - Dowling, 1992 (Box 27)
        - Elutions, undated (Box 27)
        - Ferrets, undated (Box 27)
        - Field Isolates, undated (Box 27)
        - Gels, undated (Box 27)
        - High Yield, undated (Box 27)
        - Hybridization Experiments, undated (Box 27)
        - Hyd D of IV R, 1995 (Box 27)
        - IC, undated (Box 27)
        - Leningrad, undated (Box 27)
        - Limited Genes B's (Box 27)
        - Miscellaneous Films and Genotypes, 1987-1990 (Box 27)
        - NW4, undated (Box 27)
        - Parents B's, undated (Box 27)
        - PB 2, undated (Box 27)
        - PD 12, undated (Box 27)
        - PD 13, undated (Box 27)
        - Persistent Viruses, undated (Box 27)
        - Primers, undated (Box 27)
        - RB 77, undated (Box 27)
        - RNP and P Experiments, undated (Box 27)
        - RSV, 1991-1992 (Box 27)
        - Shanghai Reassortants, 1987 (Box 27)
        - Takato's Reassortants, undated (Box 27)
        - Test Gels, undated (Box 27)
        - WT Viruses, undated (Box 27)
        - Wyeth Bivalent-Trial, 1991-1992 (Box 27)
        - Dr. Yamani, undated (Box 27)
    - Aviron
      - Series I-VIII, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2096 ]
      - Series 9-10, etc., 1997; 2 folders (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2097 ]
      - Results, Etc., 1995-1997 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous
      - E. Minuse Tissue Cultures, 1955-1964 (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2064 ]
      - Type B Strains and Lee Variations, 1958-1964 (Box 28)
      - CLA, 1961-1962 (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2062 ]
      - Case Study Details for Publication on Pericarditis, 1962 (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2063 ]
      - RAV, 1962-1969; one notebook and loose papers (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2069 ]
      - Rubella Chemotherapy, 1963-1964; 1 notebook and loose papers (Box 28)
      - Dupont Experiments, 1964-1965 (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2065 ]
      - Comparison of Cold Variant and Wild Virus in Mice, TC and Eggs, 1965-1967 (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2067 ]
      - CaK Passages and Changes to CK, 1965-1970 (Box 28)
      - Mice, Ferrets and Rabbits, 1966-1970; 2 volumes (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2070 ]
      - 3 Notebooks, 1966-1990 (Box 28)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2090 ]
      - Leighton Tubes Experiments, 1968 (Box 28)
      - Lapeer Vaccine Trials, 1968 (Box 28)
      - 5-Azacytidine, 1969-1970 (Box 28)
      - Lansing Trials, 1969-1972 (Box 29)
      - Recombination Experiment, 1970-1973; 3 volumes (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2073 ]
      - Herpes and Smallpox, 1970-1990 (Box 29)
      - Efficacy of Live Influenza Vaccine, 1972-1976 (Box 29)
      - Identification of Isolations, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
      - Type B Influenza, 1973-1987; 2 volumes (Box 29)
      - AMP and Trypsia Experiments, 1974-1977 (Box 29)
      - Swine Log Book, 1976 (Box 29)
      - Recombinants R19-R21, H22-H24, and CR22-CR24, 1976 (Box 29)
      - Nasal Vaccine Studies, 1976 (Box 29)
      - Cathy's Notebook, 1978 (Box 29)
      - MDCK Plaquing, 1978-1981; 2 volumes (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2081 ]
      - PFK, 1979 (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2079 ]
      - C. Smitka's Book, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2080 ]
      - Avian Influenza, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
      - Persistence Experiment: MDCK, 1982-1983 (Box 29)
      - Persistence Types B and C, 1984-1999; 2 volumes (Box 29)
      - Bivalent, 1983 (Box 29)
      - Baylor Study Isolates, 1984 (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2084 ]
      - Single and Double Gene Constellations of A/Du/6/83 and A/AA/6/60 7PI, 1985 (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2085 ]
      - Influenza Isolates from South Korea, 1987-1990 (Box 29)
      - ADCK and I-1-6-3PI notes, 1988 (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2088 ]
      - Flow Lot E-268 Testing B/AA/1/86, CRB 117 and CL 19-2, 1988 (Box 29)
      - National Sanitation Foundation, 1989 (Box 29)
      - High Yield Reassortants, 1989-1995 (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2095 ]
      - Virucide and Germicide Tests, 1990-1991 (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2091 ]
      - D of IV R Yield Experiments, 1991 (Box 29)
      - Subunit Vaccine / CR Vaccine Mouse Experiment, 1992 (Box 29)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2092 ]
      - Shaman Ferret Experiment, 1992 (Box 30)
      - Yoichero Experiment, 1992 (Box 30)
      - Health Service Isolates, 1993 (Box 30)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2093 ]
      - PB2 / Mutagenesis, circa 1995 (Box 30)
      - Para I-III, 1995-1999 (Box 30)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2099 ]
      - Resistance to Zanamivir in Ferrets, 1999 (Box 30)
      - Miscellaneous Notes and Data, 1967-1991; undated (Box 30)
      - Various Summaries of Influenza Vaccine Trials, undated (Box 30)
      - Various Summaries of Experiment Results, 1980-1990; undated (Box 30)